hello everyone and so in the in the next
大家好，下一个
40 minutes what we what we're going to
40分钟我们要去的是什么
do is to look at the exciting new
要做的就是看令人兴奋的新事物
features in IntelliJ how you can be more
IntelliJ中的功能如何使您变得更多
predictive whispering boot I'm guessing
我猜的预测性耳语引导
that all of you have tried spring boot
你们所有人都尝试过 spring boot
on how to look to it and when you did
关于如何看待它以及什么时候做的
that you probably have seen this website
您可能已经看过这个网站
started spring rail which is a service
启动弹簧轨道，这是一项服务
to generate ready to use projects so
生成可立即使用的项目
basically when you go to this site on
基本上，当您访问该网站时
the left you have some information about
左边你有一些信息
the project you want to generate maven
您要生成Maven的项目
coordinates or project coordinates
坐标或项目坐标
because you can use maiden or greater if
因为您可以使用处女或更大
you want to some information about the
您想要一些有关的信息
java versions you want to use the
您要使用的Java版本
language now you want to use here to
您现在要在这里使用的语言
develop in java or movie the spoon good
用java或电影开发汤匙好
versions you want to use in case you go
您想使用的版本
and just use the greatest in latest on
并使用最新的
the nightly build that's for the left
每晚的左侧建造
and on the right you have all kinds of
在右边，您有各种各样的
technologies you may choose and what
您可以选择的技术以及什么
spring boot is going to do is based on
春天的靴子要做的是基于
the presence of those libraries in your
这些库在您的存在
class pass it will try to auto configure
类传递它将尝试自动配置
other things for you so for instance if
对您来说还有其他事情，例如
you want to build a web application and
您想要构建一个Web应用程序，并且
you were to use the time leaf a certain
你一定会用时间片
path engine then you can select those
路径引擎，然后您可以选择那些
two and you can also select others you
两个，你也可以选择其他人
can look for instance also save on a
可以例如查看还保存在
deeply back end using h2 and once you do
使用h2深入后端，一旦完成
not want to dome is that you can
不想圆顶就是你可以
generate a project and that will
生成一个项目，这将
generate a zip file you can basically
生成一个zip文件，您基本上可以
put on your in your ie so that's nice
戴上你的ie，那很好
but it would be even better if you could
但是如果可以的话会更好
do all that right from into DJ and
从DJ做所有正确的事
that's the this new spring is lighter
那是这个新春天更轻
sanction here so if you click new
制裁在这里，所以，如果您单击新建
project spring initializer you'll
项目弹簧初始化器
basically get the same features right
基本上得到正确的功能
for my wife run into hid so this is just
因为我的妻子被藏起来，所以这仅仅是
dko you want to choose and the site but
您要选择的dko和网站，但
the same size
一样大小
we saw before and you can see the same
我们之前见过，你可以看到相同的
information i'm going to choose java 8
信息，我要选择java 8
for instance and keep moving from now
例如，从现在起继续前进
and what we're going to do to showcase
以及我们要做的展示
the features of IntelliJ we're going to
我们将要介绍的IntelliJ的功能
build a web app and we're going to
建立一个网络应用程序，我们将
create very very quickly an entity a GP
很快创建一个实体GP
entity and we are going to create a
实体，我们将创建一个
repository for that and we're going to
仓库，我们将
usage to as the data stone we're also
用作数据石，我们也是
going to secure this web app and we're
将要保护此网络应用程序，我们
also going to expose the repository as a
也将仓库公开为
rest endpoint and finally what we're
剩下的终点，最后是我们
going to do is we're going to choose
我们要做的是选择
also this library called the actuator
该库也称为执行器
and what it provides is it provides all
它提供的是它提供所有
kind of moving functional features all
一种移动功能，全部
kinds of services that you have to do
您必须要做的各种服务
over and over again when you start a new
一遍又一遍地开始新的
application so the idea instead of do
应用程序，所以这个想法而不是做
those over and over again you have have
那些一遍又一遍的
them provided to you so these are the
他们提供给您，所以这些是
technologies I want to use today and i'm
我今天想使用的技术
going to say i want to create a project
要说我想创建一个项目
min demo IntelliJ ready and have that
分钟演示IntelliJ准备好了
into that directory and click finish
进入该目录，然后单击完成
some time
一段时间
my new project right right from here
我的新项目就在这里
from eie the metal project has been
从eie金属项目已经
detected so I'm going to add that and I
检测到，所以我要添加它，然后我
have a fully functional project I can
我可以有一个功能齐全的项目
use right away so if you know about
立即使用，所以如果您知道
spring would you know that the way to
春天你知道那条路吗
start a good application is mostly it's
开始一个好的应用程序主要是
very simple it's like to right click
非常简单，就像右键单击一样
right click main and your application
右键单击main和您的应用程序
will stop regardless of the fact its web
不管它的网站是什么都会停止
application or not because we provide an
是否提供应用程序，因为我们提供了
embedded container for you if you decide
如果您决定使用嵌入式容器
to build up with that so I'm going to
用它来建立，所以我要
create quickly the entity i was talking
快速创建我正在谈论的实体
about earlier and i'm going to create a
大约早些时候，我将创建一个
speaker and in order not to write the
演讲者，为了不写
class in front of you i'm going to use
在你面前我要使用的课程
an integer called 5 template which
称为5模板的整数
basically allows me to create a class
基本上可以让我创建一个类
from a pre-populated template so you can
从预先填充的模板中
see that the speaker is a regular GP
看到扬声器是普通的GP
entity i was in an ID first name last
实体我的ID名姓
name a twitter account for friends and a
为朋友命名一个Twitter帐户，并为
bio i'm going also to create a speaker
我也要去创造一个扬声器
repository and the same thing and the
仓库和相同的东西和
speaker repository is using spring data
扬声器存储库正在使用Spring数据
as spring data GPA in this case even
甚至在这种情况下作为春季数据GPA
though you see no import whatsoever
虽然您看不到任何汇入
related to GPA so it's a regular
与GPA有关，所以这是常规
critical story on a speaker depravities
演讲者堕落的批评故事
long if you know about open data you
只要您知道开放数据，
know that you can define methods on the
知道您可以在
repository interface and spring data
仓库接口和Spring数据
will create a proxy for you and will
将为您创建一个代理，并将
ensure the proper priorities based on
确保基于
the method name so basically this is
方法名称，基本上，这是
going to create a search methods on the
要在
Twitter field and it will return a
Twitter字段，它将返回一个
single speaker and the same thing here
单扬声器和这里的同一件事
returning a collection of speakers
返回演讲者集合
having the specified last name you can
具有指定的姓氏，您可以
also see that it has some spring data
还看到它有一些弹簧数据
repository annotations on it which in
关于它的存储库注释
this case is simply used to customize
这种情况只是用来自定义
the way the search method is going to be
搜索方法的方式
exposed when you're going to see that in
当你要看到它时暴露
a minute
一分钟
and these are to bind the URI attribute
这些将绑定URI属性
to the actual search parameter so I want
到实际的搜索参数，所以我想要
to have some speaker in my stall as you
跟你一样在我的摊位上讲一些话
see i'm going to use h2 so to do that
看到我要使用H2，所以要这样做
I'm going to use a another neat feature
我将使用另一个简洁功能
if you create a file named imported
如果您创建一个名为import的文件
sequin at the root of the classpath and
亮片在类路径的根和
having it is going to generate the
有它会产生
schema if it finds such file it will
模式，如果找到这样的文件，它将
basically process it and to to fill it
基本处理并填充它
i'm going to use it another feature
我将使用它的另一个功能
called life template where you can
可以在其中称为生活模板
basically map any shortcut to whatever
基本上将任何快捷方式映射到任何内容
you want this is it added up so I'm
你想要这个加起来，所以我
going to run it as you can see as from
如您所见，将运行它
into the GID 40-minute one year later
一年后40分钟进入GID
has detected that this main class is a
已检测到该主要类别为
spring good application so it offers a
春天很好的应用程序，所以它提供了一个
way to start it as an a spring boot
将其作为弹簧靴启动的方式
application as the icon stake here so
应用程序作为图标在这里
let's do that okay so i have an
那样做吧，我有一个
application
应用
which is starting now doing some stuff
现在开始做一些事情
okay so I need to log in to my appt the
好的，所以我需要登录到我的应用
reason why I need to look into my appt
我需要研究我的appt的原因
is because I've added the security
是因为我添加了安全性
starter in the list in the weather
天气列表中的首发
previously so the decision that boat is
以前所以决定船是
going to take if you don't have any
如果没有的话
special configuration or any special
特殊配置或任何特殊
customizations to your app is to secure
对您的应用进行自定义是为了确保安全
everything with basic authentication and
具有基本身份验证的一切
it's also going to create a user that
它也将创建一个用户
you can at least log in to your
您至少可以登录到
applications and the default user using
应用程序和默认用户使用
in this user and there's the default
在这个用户中，有默认
password because if we do that and we
密码，因为如果这样做，我们
write a default password in our
在我们的密码中写一个默认密码
documentation and someone happens to
文档，有人碰巧
forget about it then it's it's a
忘了它，那是一个
security or it can be dangerous so what
安全或可能很危险，那又如何
we do is whenever we start the app we
我们要做的就是每当我们启动应用程序时
generate a unique password for that
为此生成一个唯一的密码
instance so if we start the app again
因此，如果我们再次启动该应用程序
the password will change so I'm going to
密码将更改，所以我要
copy that wait here and then I can log
复制在这里等待，然后我可以登录
into my app so i can see that the
进入我的应用程序，这样我就可以看到
repository the speaker repository has
发言人存储库具有的存储库
been exposed and i can see that the
被暴露了，我可以看到
speakers i have created through that
我通过它创建的扬声器
encoded support file I've been processed
我已经处理过的编码支持文件
and can be seen as a restful resource I
可以看作是一种宁静的资源
can also navigate to such methods
也可以导航到此类方法
through that link and I can see the two
通过该链接，我可以看到两个
of such metal that have been exposed so
如此暴露的金属
by Twitter and cyber last name so i can
通过Twitter和网络姓氏，这样我就可以
also search by Twitter and cell phone
还通过Twitter和手机搜索
Tricia and happy here I told you also
翠西亚（Tricia）和我在这里告诉你的快乐
about the actuator and what the actuator
关于执行器以及执行器是什么
is provide is certain endpoints like the
提供某些端点，例如
info in points which gives some
信息点，这给了一些
information about your app on earth
有关您的应用在地球上的信息
standpoint that checks if your app is up
立场检查您的应用程序是否启动
and running I can see that each two
运行，我可以看到每两个
databases up and some information about
数据库和有关的一些信息
disk disk space I can
我可以的磁盘空间
I can look for some metrics etc etc okay
我可以寻找一些指标等，好吗
so that that was a spring boot up I took
所以那是我的 spring boot
10 minutes to build it from the ground
10分钟从地面建造
up even though I chiquita bit with the
即使我在基基塔咬了一下
templates but you get the idea so the
模板，但是您有了主意，因此
first thing which is really annoying
第一件事真的很烦
about this this application is every
关于这个应用程序是每一个
time it starts it requires you to look
时间开始，它需要你看看
into the lab to find out about the
进入实验室以了解有关
default password so of course you know
默认密码，所以您当然知道
in a regular app what you would do is
在常规应用中，您将要做的是
create a proper security configuration
创建适当的安全配置
when I'm going to do that so one thing
当我要这样做时，一件事
about the springboard auto-configuration
关于跳板自动配置
mechanism is when you want to use the
机制是当您想使用
auto configuration and so you want to
自动配置，所以你想
keep what you have to configuration does
保留您要配置的内容
but you want to slightly customize it
但您想稍微自定义它
each other configuration night expose a
彼此配置晚上暴露出一个
set of configuration keys and by
配置键集和
specifying some customization using
使用指定一些自定义
those keys you can slightly change the
这些键，您可以稍微改变
way due to configuration works so the
由于配置有效，所以
first thing I want to do is I want to
我想做的第一件事是
specify a password instead of having an
指定密码，而不要输入密码
auto-generated phone so I need to know
自动生成的电话，所以我需要知道
the key I need to know which King maps
我需要知道哪个国王映射的关键
to the future and I first I need to know
未来，我首先我需要知道
if your teacher exist so what I'm going
如果你的老师存在，那么我要去的地方
to do is try to type pass and see what
要做的是尝试输入pass看看
happens and what you get in IntelliJ
发生，您在IntelliJ中得到了什么
IDEA 14 load fun is this content assist
IDEA 14加载乐趣是此内容的帮助
for configuration keys you can see that
对于配置密钥，您可以看到
the first entry here is a security don't
这里的第一项是安全性
use or the password and you have some
使用或密码，你有一些
documentation saying it's the password
说明这是密码的文档
for the default username you also have
对于默认用户名，您也可以使用
the type you so let's let's fix it to
这样的类型，让我们将其修复为
change me so instead of having this auto
改变我，所以不用这个自动
configure to password auto generated
配置为自动生成密码
password sorry you have a one you fix
密码抱歉，您有一个要修复的密码
yourself then I want to change the real
你自己，我想改变真正的
for whatever reason and if I time will
无论出于什么原因，如果我愿意的话
then i will get the default value you
然后我将获得默认值
may have noticed that when i had to log
可能已经注意到，当我不得不登录时
in that pop-up set spring so I want to
在那个弹出窗口中，所以我想
do something I want
做我想做的事
say hello and choose a random value and
打个招呼并选择一个随机值，然后
spring boot as this report for the
春季启动，因为此报告
random prefix which is a special prefix
随机前缀，这是一个特殊的前缀
you can use in application of properties
您可以在属性的应用中使用
so it knows about it and it auto
所以它知道并自动
completes things for you then I want to
为你完成事情，然后我想
specify the roles that the user will
指定用户将要扮演的角色
have and it's very important that this
拥有，这一点非常重要
user has the admin role because that's
用户具有管理员角色，因为
the role that's required to access the
访问该角色所需的角色
actuator a point so deep in for the info
执行器的信息如此深入
earth matrix endpoint I just show you so
地球矩阵端点我只是告诉你
let's type role now can see here that I
让我们键入角色现在可以在这里看到我
have security use of the troll which is
安全使用巨魔
a list and in that case since it's a
一个列表，在这种情况下，因为它是一个
list intelligent knows about it and say
列出聪明的人知道并说
I'm going to say user for this one and
我要说这个的用户
i'm going to type whatever something
我要输入任何东西
that's not a valid number and oh I can
这不是一个有效的数字，哦，我可以
also type 0 of course that won't work
当然也输入0是行不通的
just the same key and I got me so
一样的钥匙，我就这样
remember this influent I was talking
记得我在说这个有影响力的东西
about there is a way to set some data
关于有一种方法可以设置一些数据
into JSON output and the way it works if
转换成JSON输出及其工作方式
you look at the spring good
你看着春天好
documentation is you will need to set a
文档是您将需要设置一个
key oops prefixes info so info dot
关键命令前缀信息，所以信息点
anything will be set as a value to that
任何东西都将被设置为该值
JSON output so if i tap info then i can
JSON输出，所以如果我点击信息，那么我可以
see it's a nap and have some
看到这是午睡，有一些
documentation about it so let's say i'm
关于它的文档，所以说我
going to type some description you can
可以输入一些描述
see that the the description key here is
看到这里的描述键是
displayed differently so that you know
显示方式不同，以便您知道
it's two key of a map and let's say i
这是一张地图的两个关键，假设我
want to create a property on my own
想自己创建一个属性
which is displayed as being unknown okay
显示为未知好吗
and let's say i want to show that as a
假设我想将其显示为
value so i get this
值，所以我得到这个
auto completion as well for
自动完成
configuration in case you may create
配置，以防您可能创建
yourself and you can see the default
你自己，你可以看到默认
value in this case while the actual
在这种情况下的价值，而实际
value in this case okay another map
在这种情况下的价值还可以
special ending that IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA的特殊结局
support is the logging level feature so
支持是日志记录级别功能，因此
it's a way in spring boot to configure
这是在Spring Boot中进行配置的一种方式
the logging regardless of the logging
记录而不管记录
library that you use whether you lose
您是否会失去使用的库
work for Jay load back or something else
为Jay加载工作或其他工作
you can specify some levels here and we
您可以在此处指定一些级别，我们
will configure that according to the
将根据
logging infrastructure that you have at
您拥有的日志记录基础架构
runtime and the tool knows about it so
运行时，该工具对此有所了解
it offers you again nice auto completion
它再次为您提供了很好的自动完成功能
for the package in this case and the
对于这种情况下的包装以及
value alright so let's start this
好的价值，让我们开始吧
application again with all those
所有这些再次申请
customizations and see what happens so
定制，看看会发生什么
the first thing that we should see is
我们应该看到的第一件事是
some additional information in the logs
日志中的一些其他信息
and this is the auto configuration
这是自动配置
report from this package actually since
实际上是因为
I switched if since I switched that
我切换了如果因为我切换了那个
package to debug so let's say I'm have
包进行调试，所以说我有
to log in again so its user change okay
重新登录，以便其用户可以更改
change me and you can also see here that
改变我，你也可以在这里看到
the realme says ello 3 which is all of
领域说ello 3这就是全部
the random value between 0 0 5
0 0 5之间的随机值
to do in foreign point I can see the
在异国情调下我可以看到
values that have set okay and I still
设置好的值，我仍然
have a warning on into my configuration
对我的配置发出警告
file and this morning and I could also
文件，今天早上，我也可以
type some crap here and have an error
在这里输入一些废话，并有一个错误
instead and it would be nice it IntelliJ
相反，IntelliJ会很好
IDEA could actually validate that file
IDEA实际上可以验证该文件
on built so there is a way to do that
内置的，所以有一种方法可以做到
the first thing you have to do is you
你要做的第一件事就是你
have to make sure that under the belt
必须确保在皮带下
execution deployment and compiler
执行部署和编译器
section there is a validation subsection
部分有一个验证子部分
and revalidate on built that you have to
并重新验证您必须建立的
need to enable for it to work and what
需要启用它才能正常工作
we interested in this case is the spring
我们对这种情况感兴趣的是春天
models but i'll just keep the other ones
模型，但我会保留其他模型
so now once you make sure that the
所以现在一旦您确保
feature is enabled in new instance and
在新实例中启用了功能，并且
you have to go to project structure
你必须去项目结构
facets create a new spring facet for
方面为创建新的春天方面
your module basically and then add an
您的模块基本上，然后添加一个
additional property file which is the
其他属性文件是
file that we are currently editing so
我们当前正在编辑的文件
this one okay so if i do that and i
这个好吧，如果我这样做，我
dealt now i can see that the warning has
现在处理，我可以看到警告有
been integrated into the main make
被整合到主要品牌
window and i can also try to start the
窗口，我也可以尝试启动
application and it won't start because
应用程序，它将无法启动，因为
something is wrong in my configuration
我的配置有问题
but we
但是我们
really fix the warning on a liquid and
确实将警告修正为液体
what I want to show you now is you may
我现在想告诉你的是你可能
wonder by now how hunting EG ID is
现在想知道如何狩猎EG ID
actually building the pissed so when you
实际上建造小便，所以当你
type something how does it know about
输入一些有关它的信息
all those keys and one thing which is
所有这些键和一件事是
really really nice to what we built is
对我们建造的来说真的非常好
it's actually an open infrastructure or
它实际上是一个开放的基础架构
something you can use in your own
您可以自己使用的东西
project something you can use for your
投射一些可以用于您的东西
only keys and it's really easy to do it
只有按键，真的很容易做到
going to show you that in a minute what
一会儿告诉你
happens really is spring boot as of
真的是从春天开始
version one the to generate metadata for
版本1为其生成元数据
each configuration keys that defines and
定义和定义的每个配置键
it generates that with a standard format
它以标准格式生成
a JSON format and it generates a fine in
JSON格式，它会在
a specific location and what IntelliJ
具体位置和什么IntelliJ
IDEA does is looking for that file for
IDEA确实正在寻找该文件
each jar in your project and basically
项目中的每个罐子，基本上
build a repository of configuration keys
建立配置密钥库
there is two way to do it there is a
有两种方法可以做到
manual way for corner cases that's what
手动处理极端情况
I'm going to show you now even though
我现在要告诉你
that's not what you what you're supposed
那不是你应该的
to do you you you should aim that deal
做你，你应该瞄准那笔交易
to make it solution but I want to show
使其成为解决方案，但我想展示
you the manual one first so you have an
您先来一份手册，以便
intention here so if you ask the tool
意图在这里，所以如果你问这个工具
what you can do it offers you a way to
您可以做什么，为您提供了一种
define the configuration key and to do
定义配置键并执行
that again spring booth as defined that
再次定义的春季展位
standardization is you may place a file
标准化是您可以放置​​文件
called additional configuration spring
称为附加配置弹簧
configuration little a tattoo Jason into
配置小纹身杰森成
a Demeter inch directory and we will
一个Demeter inch目录，我们将
look that up and use those as additional
查找并将其用作附加内容
with manual metadata so since the five
加上手动元数据
does not exist for this project gid asks
这个项目不存在，女童问
me if I want to create it and it also
我，如果我想创建它，它也
asked me where I want to create it and
问我要在哪里创建它，
it will basically generate a sample
它基本上会产生一个样本
entry for me so we already said that the
入门，所以我们已经说过
counter it's probably an integer right
计数器可能是整数对
not a string so
不是字符串，所以
I can make that a string and I can also
我可以把它做成字符串，也可以
have a default value which is different
具有不同的默认值
from 42 I could also let's say create a
从42我也可以说创建一个
different property of type string this
字符串类型的不同属性
time and some it's a very small
时间，有些时间很小
description you may have noticed by now
您可能已经注意到的描述
that there is a banner on the top
顶部有一个横幅
telling you hey you should rerun the
告诉您嘿，您应该重新运行
annotation processor to update to update
批注处理器要更新要更新
a meta data so the way it works is we've
元数据，所以它的工作方式是
implemented an annotation processor that
实现了一个注释处理器
well is as part of the build and when it
好是作为构建的一部分，当它
detects either the additional metadata
检测其他元数据
fine all some annotated class we're
罚款我们所有的注释类
going to i'm going to show you that in a
我要向你展示
minute it will generate amid a metadata
分钟，它将在元数据中生成
file and place it at the standard
归档并将其放置在标准位置
rotation so in order to add that to your
旋转，以便将其添加到您的
project it's very simple you only need
项目，这很简单，您只需要
to add 11 dependency which is I'm going
添加11个依赖关系
to do now and it's called spring boot
现在要做的就是所谓的弹簧靴
configuration processor and since it's
配置处理器，因为它是
an annotation processor it runs as part
作为一部分运行的注释处理器
of your belt reading you don't need to
不需要阅读
expose that to your project at all it's
完全暴露给您的项目
really something that's local to the
真的是本地的东西
project used by the build process of
构建过程使用的项目
your project and not exposed as a
您的项目，而不是暴露为
library that's required to use your app
使用您的应用程序所需的库
ok so I did create an additional key and
好的，所以我确实创建了一个额外的密钥，
see that the file has been generated
看到文件已经生成
here so if i go back and type football I
在这里，所以如果我回去输入足球
can find my additional description here
可以在这里找到我的其他描述
but well you need to manually add those
但是，您需要手动添加这些
metadata by hand you may also change
您也可以手动更改元数据
your code and in the makeup you forget
您的代码和妆容，您会忘记
to change the metadata so it's it's
更改元数据，就是这样
really a bit painful so what I want to
真的有点痛苦，所以我想
show you is how you can use that feature
向您展示如何使用该功能
and and have the metadata generated from
并且具有从生成的元数据
for you from the curly so to do that to
为您从卷曲中做到这一点
do that I'm going to create a simple
为此，我将创建一个简单的
service a little service going to flag
服务一点服务要标记
that other service and use the command
该其他服务并使用命令
line runner interface from spring good
Spring的LineRunner接口好
what's basically going to happen is when
基本上要发生的是什么时候
the application will start I will this
该应用程序将启动，我会这样
particular method will be called so I
特定的方法将被调用，所以我
want to say hello but I want to say
想打个招呼，但我想说
hello in a customized way so let's say I
用一种定制的方式打招呼
have a you know properties class and
有一个你知道的属性类
let's create that class it basically has
让我们创建它基本上具有的类
a prefix let's say it hello and it has a
一个前缀，我们打个招呼，它有一个
target so the read the thing to which
目标，所以读到的东西
you want to say hello to let's use that
你想打个招呼，让我们使用它
within our hello service I'm going to
在我们的服务中，我要
inject the yellow properties which if
注入黄色属性，如果
you follow count work because other
你跟随计数工作，因为其他
property is not annotated by any means
不以任何方式注释属性
so we will come back to that in a minute
所以我们稍后再讲
and let's say I'm going to do prefix a
假设我要给前缀a
space and the target simple there's a
空间和简单的目标
few things that's missing the first
缺少的第一件事
thing is we want to tell spring boot
事情是我们要告诉春天引导
that this class is actually to be mapped
该类实际上是要映射的
by configuration
通过配置
is defined in your configuration so in a
是在您的配置中定义的，因此在
command-line switch in the system
系统中的命令行开关
property or in an entry in this file the
属性或此文件中的条目
application properties file so I'm going
应用程序属性文件，所以我要去
to add an annotation from springwood
从springwood添加注释
called configuration properties with a
称为配置属性
prefix and as you may have found on by
前缀，您可能会在上找到
now this particular configuration key is
现在，这个特定的配置密钥是
ello dot prefix and this one is a load
ello点前缀，这是一个负载
of target that doesn't mean that this
目标并不意味着这个
configuration properties is processed by
配置属性由
any means there is an extra annotations
任何手段都有一个额外的注释
to use to do that and that's also going
用来做到这一点，这也正在
to make sure that this pot this
确保这个锅这个
particular class is a spring wind which
一类是春风
make sure that you auto wearing I just
确保你自动穿着我
hear will work there is no target being
听到会工作，没有目标
defined and I want to make sure its
定义，我想确保它
monetary to define one so I'm going to
金钱来定义一个，所以我要
add a constraint to that property and
向该属性添加约束，然后
let's start my app again and you can see
让我们再次启动我的应用程序，您可以看到
that the one is gone now and that should
那一个现在不见了，应该
fail and that fails because target is
失败了，那失败了，因为目标是
not set okay so let's go back to my file
设置不好，让我们回到我的文件
and you can see that it's already there
你会看到它已经在那里
so the thing that the annotation
这样的东西，注解
processor is looking at is this
处理器正在看的是这个
configuration properties annotation so
配置属性注释
whenever you put that on the class in
每当你把它放在课堂上
your project the annotation processor
您的项目注释处理器
will detect it's a target for
会检测到它是目标
configuration kids and it will generate
配置孩子，它将生成
the relevant metadata so good you've
相关元数据太好了
seen that I had to create together in a
看到我必须一起创造
setter in order to inject the value so
为了注入值的二传手
if you have a feel for instance without
如果您有没有
a setter springwood won't be able to
二传手斯普林伍德将无法
inject the value so it won't generate a
注入值，这样就不会产生
metadata for that either you can
该拉屎的元数据可以
also see that the default value has been
还可以看到默认值是
found muttering so it's a world
发现喃喃自语，所以这是一个世界
striding okay then i can see that i have
大步走好，然后我可以看到我有
my message here you can also add the
我在这里的消息，您还可以添加
documentation in a certain place so that
文档在某个地方，以便
the annotation processor can pick that
注释处理器可以选择
up the reason why we do that versus
我们这样做的原因与
looking at the Javadoc ano setter is you
看着Javadoc ano setter是
may want to provide a very dedicated
可能想提供一个非常专注的
message to the configuration keys
消息到配置键
without impacting the way you call this
不会影响您的称呼方式
build so without in having to change the
建立，而无需更改
way the setter is cool oops so if I go
二传手很酷，所以如果我去
do that I do that again sorry then I get
这样做，我再次这样做，对不起，然后我得到
the documentation for my field and you
我和您的领域的文档
can see that the arrow target is gone
可以看到箭头目标消失了
now because since you have defined it
现在，因为您已经定义了它
already in your in this particular
已经在您这里
configuration it will be shipped around
配置它将被运送到周围
automatically by imaging so that's for
通过成像自动进行，因此
the configuration king and the content
配置王和内容
assistance support that intellij idea
协助支持intellij的想法
provides one thing also that and we saw
还提供了一件事，我们看到了
that the early beginning intellij i
那早期的intellij我
support is a dedicated run configuration
支持是专用的运行配置
for spring boot applications so let's
对于春季启动应用程序，让我们
see let's see that now you can see it
看到让我们看到，现在您可以看到它
it's quite a similar to a regular main
这与常规主管道非常相似
class configuration they not but there
类配置他们不是，但那里
are more data here and dedicated options
这里有更多数据和专用选项
I can hide the banner and I can also
我可以隐藏横幅，也可以
change / run configuration some settings
更改/运行配置一些设置
and I get also content and systems in
我也得到了内容和系统
here so let's say that for this path for
在这里，让我们说这个
this particular instance I want to
我想要这个特定的实例
change the password
修改密码
okay and let's run this application
好吧，让我们运行这个应用程序
again and if i go here i have to login
再次，如果我去这里，我必须登录
again you see that the value has changed
再次，您看到值已更改
hopefully and that's changed me too
希望这也改变了我
anyway go so these are really a good way
无论如何，所以这些确实是个好方法
for you to if you have multiple ways of
如果您有多种方式
starting a particular spring boot
启动特定的弹簧靴
application and if you want to change
应用程序以及是否要更改
some settings you can do so directly
您可以直接进行某些设置
here and have multiple run configuration
在这里并有多个运行配置
for the same app with slightly different
对于同一个应用，但略有不同
settings another thing that IntelliJ
设置另一件事，IntelliJ
IDEA knows about is profiles so profiles
IDEA知道配置文件，因此配置文件
it's not something that's you it's
那不是你，而是
therefore since presence of spring
因此，由于春天的存在
framework 322 and the way it works is
框架322及其工作方式是
you can start an application by
您可以通过以下方式启动应用程序
specifying a set of profile profile
指定一组配置文件配置文件
names battery and when those names are
给电池起名字，什么时候起名字
present bins that are flagged as being
当前标记为存在的垃圾箱
defined for certain profile will be
为某些配置文件定义的将是
enabled spring boot takes that support a
启用的Spring Boot需要支持
bit further and allows you to create
更进一步，让您创建
configuration file with the name of the
具有以下名称的配置文件
Prophet with the name of the profile in
先知中的个人资料名称
it so let's say that I want to create a
因此，假设我要创建一个
death profile and the first thing I want
死亡概况和我想要的第一件事
to do is I want to disable auto
我要做的是禁用自动
education completely and in this case
完全教育，在这种情况下
there is a key which is this one which
有一个钥匙就是这个
is on by default and I'm going to switch
默认是打开的，我要切换
that off
那关
I would like also to show you an extra
我也想给你看一个额外的
being definition and I'm going to use
被定义，我将使用
the life stamp late again and what we're
生活印记又迟了，我们是什么
going to do when the Deaf profile is and
当聋人档案是和
ever is we're going to expose the h2
曾经是我们要暴露H2
console so that you can actually log in
控制台，以便您实际上可以登录
through your web application to look at
通过您的Web应用程序来查看
the state of the database it's it's
数据库的状态是
useful in development so since I want to
在开发中很有用，所以既然我想
use h 2 i need to remove this scope here
使用h 2我需要在这里删除此范围
so that i can access the edge to console
这样我就可以访问控制台的边缘
a class and I have this life template
一堂课，我有这个生活模板
with a parameter called h2 console and
使用名为h2 console的参数
when I do that the only thing I have to
当我这样做时，我唯一要做的就是
do is give the name of the profile and
要做的就是提供配置文件的名称，然后
this register and extracts orbit on the
该寄存器并提取轨道上的
console path so let's start this
控制台路径，所以让我们开始吧
application again without specifying any
再次申请，但未指定任何
profile just to prove that it's not
个人资料只是为了证明它不是
doing something it shouldn't and then
做一些不该做的事，然后
you can go window I have to log in again
您可以进入窗口，我必须再次登录
and that's change me too and if i go on
这也改变了我，如果我继续
console doesn't work there is no mapping
控制台不起作用，没有映射
for that so let's go back to the run
为此，让我们回到运行
configuration here and let's duplicate
配置在这里，让我们重复
the different configuration and call it
不同的配置并调用它
that and then here i can basically say
那然后在这里我基本上可以说
that i want to activate the death
我想激活死亡
profile it's from this app and open a
对此应用进行配置，然后打开
new incognito window so the
新的隐身窗口，因此
the new application is not secure
新应用程序不安全
anymore and I can go to the console and
我可以去控制台了
actually look at my ski curtain but
看着我的滑雪帘，但是
IntelliJ IDEA goes a bit further than
IntelliJ IDEA比
that and it also knows about a deaf
那也知道聋人
profile value in certain places so if
在某些地方的配置文件值，如果
you want to rename this value here so
您想在此处重命名此值，以便
let's say you want to call that dev tool
假设您要调用该开发工具
for whatever reason then it will find
无论出于什么原因，它将发现
out that in your project there is
在您的项目中
already a file respecting that
已经是一个尊重这一点的文件
convention file for the Deaf profile and
聋人档案的常规文件和
it will suggest you to rename the file
它会建议您重命名文件
as well since you change the name of
以及因为您更改了名称
that profile okay um I have a few more
那个人资料好吧，我还有几个
things I want to show you which is
我想告诉你的是
called a smart content assist so that's
称为智能内容辅助，因此
basically the the ability of into the
基本上有能力
GID to knows about certain types and to
GID了解某些类型，并
offer Smart Auto completion of each
提供每个的智能自动完成
other key on the value so for instance
值上的其他键，例如
you also notice that we have a
您还注意到我们有一个
deprecated support so if you have a key
不建议使用的支持，因此如果您有钥匙
and you want to no longer to support it
而你不想再支持它
but of course you still need to support
但是当然您仍然需要支持
it from from quite some time then you
从很长一段时间开始
can flag that as a deprecated in it will
可以将其标记为已弃用
be shown with another strike let's
被示为另一次罢工，让我们
customize that key and in this case it's
自定义该键，在这种情况下
in socal set I can basically change the
在Socal Set中，我基本上可以更改
I can have a look suggestion for the
我可以看看建议
other castle value can also do that with
其他城堡的价值也可以做到这一点
content types so in this case the
内容类型，因此在这种情况下
content type of the default content type
默认内容类型的内容类型
of timely cubes
及时的多维数据集
the value I don't know excuse me
我不知道的价值对不起
whatever but we also have a smart auto
随便什么，但我们也有一个智能汽车
completion for values potential values
完成价值的潜在价值
for T so you you probably used
T，所以你可能用过
hibernating the past and you know that
冬眠的过去，你知道
there is this setting that allows you to
有此设置，您可以
create or update the database on startup
启动时创建或更新数据库
or maybe not not do anything you also
或者也许你什么也不做
notice that I didn't have to do anything
注意，我不需要做任何事情
the reason why I didn't have to
我不必这么做的原因
customize anything is because when
自定义任何内容是因为
spring boot tried to auto configure the
Spring Boot试图自动配置
datasource it first looked at the
首先查看的数据源
context there was no data salty fine I
上下文中没有数据咸我
didn't define anything then start
没有定义任何东西然后开始
looking at the cross paths and found
看着十字路口，发现
that there was one embedded database so
那里只有一个嵌入式数据库
since nothing was defying it created
因为没有什么可以抗拒它
database in memory for me with a default
默认情况下为我在内存中存储数据库
name which is test DD you saw that in
您在其中看到的测试DD名称
the console and since it's a database in
控制台，因为它是数据库
memory so you're going to be recreate
内存，所以您将被重新创建
recreate that everyone that auto
重新创建每个自动的人
configuration piece is actually also
配置片实际上也是
enabling the generation of the scheme
促成方案的产生
automatically so that you get what you
自动地，以便您得到您所得到的
basically expect without specifying
基本上期望不指定
anything so if i type have a neck here i
任何东西，如果我键入在这里有脖子我
can see that i can provide some values
可以看到我可以提供一些价值
hood and i get auto completion for those
引擎盖，我为那些自动完成
i can also navigate to the actual target
我也可以导航到实际目标
of the key so for instance exactly the
的关键，因此例如
same way as you do when you want to grow
与您想要成长时一样
through a method call method invocation
通过方法调用方法调用
so if i do this i'm basically going into
所以如果我这样做，我基本上会进入
the security properties of springwood
弹跳木的安全特性
and the set password so i can see what
和设置的密码，这样我就可以看到
happens when i set that key i also have
当我设置该键时也会发生
a quick documentation assist for the key
钥匙的快速文档帮助
with the default value the description
使用默认值说明
alright so that's what I wanted to show
好了，这就是我想展示的
you today the upcoming support well it's
您今天即将获得的支持是
released now it's into j-14 dot one
现在发布，它进入j-14点一
final by the way so if you don't load
顺便说一句，所以如果你不加载
that versions right away you get all
那个版本马上就可以得到所有
those features right now and let's see
这些功能现在，让我们看看
if there is i'm sure there are tons of
如果有，我确定有很多
questions i could hopefully answer so
我希望可以回答的问题
let's see about that thank you Stefan
让我们来看看谢谢斯特凡
hello this is this is rob ah I can show
你好，这是抢劫啊，我可以证明
just for you okay great um so there's
只是为了您，好吧，所以
one question i'm popping in here so i'm
我在这里弹出一个问题，所以我
not sure if he answered this ready it
不知道他是否准备好了
says don't we need to add config classes
说我们不需要添加配置类
to spring facet well i didn't add it
春天方面很好，我没有添加
because I it was not the goal here but
因为我这不是这里的目标，而是
you don't have to if you added then you
您不必添加就可以了
get additional content assist but that's
获得更多内容帮助，但这就是
regular spring support not spring boot
常规弹簧支撑而不是弹簧靴
related so if you add that application
相关，所以如果您添加该应用程序
that demo application class and you
该演示应用程序类，您
define beans in them the IntelliJ IDEA
在其中定义Bean IntelliJ IDEA
knows about knows about them and can see
知道关于他们的知识并可以看到
when you try to inject again where it's
当您尝试再次注射到哪里时
coming from and things like that but in
来自这样的事情，但在
the case of what i wanted to demo it's
我想演示的情况是
not mandatory okay i think you entered
不是强制性的，好吧，我认为您已经输入
this one are you going to put code at
这个你要把代码放在
github yeah i'm going to do that i'm
是的，我要做到这一点
going to propose the dis exact app so
将提出不确切的应用程序，所以
that you can play with it right after to
你可以马上玩
let me know okay there's another
让我知道好吧，还有另一个
question here how Grails fits the spring
这里的问题是Grails如何适应春天
ecosystem okay well if you look at Grail
看看Grail，生态系统还可以
is actually great three dot 0 or was
实际上是伟大的三点0或
released today and it's a rewrite on top
今天发布，上面是重写
of spring boots so if you use grid 3
spring boot ，所以如果您使用网格3
it's basically generates all basically
它基本上生成所有
uses spring good behind the scenes which
在后台使用良好的春天
means that your greatest 3 app is
表示您最大的3个应用是
actually a spring would have so it's
其实春天会有
very central in the way boot is used
引导方式非常关键
okay okay the questions are coming in
好吧好吧问题来了
now here let's see I can see one
现在在这里，让我看一看
regarding spring-loaded I can maybe
关于弹簧加载我可能
answer right away suggestion is all can
马上回答建议就可以了
we add spring load it in IntelliJ by VM
我们通过VM在IntelliJ中添加弹簧加载
parameters so the answer is yes you
参数，所以答案是肯定的
basically need to don't know don't know
基本上需要不知道不知道
spring loaded it's a single job put that
春季加载这是一项工作
draw on somewhere on your desk and in
画在桌子上的某个地方
the run configuration there is to flag
运行配置有标记
in which I'll define on the spring
我将在春天定义
loaded with me you define them as the vm
与我一起加载，您将它们定义为虚拟机
options and spring loaded will start at
选项和弹簧加载将开始于
the same time as you're ok the next
下次还可以的话
question does the community version
问题社区版本
provides spring boot integration as far
提供到目前为止的Spring Boot集成
as I know the older spring supports is
我知道较早的弹簧支撑是
related to the your teammate version so
与您的队友版本有关
the spring good version goes with it but
春天不错的版本，但
I guess someone from jetbrains is more
我猜是来自捷脑的人
suited to answer that i'm actually using
适合回答我实际使用的
the ultimate version I don't sing that
我不唱歌的终极版本
the open to the free versions as the
向免费版本开放
feature ok how would I add some user
功能确定，我如何添加一些用户
name password authentication backed by
由支持的名称密码身份验证
example a database table or a custom
例如数据库表或自定义
user detail service ok so you can still
用户详细信息服务确定，因此您仍然可以
see my screen right yes incorrect all
看到我的屏幕对不对所有
right ok great so you would do something
好吧，很好，你会做点什么
like this you would create a security
这样，您将创建一个证券
config global piano put that down so you
配置全局钢琴让您失望
would basically give your opinion to
基本上会给您意见
spring boot you would say i don't want
春季靴，你会说我不想
spring good to auto configure the
春天好自动配置
security for me i want i want to define
对我来说，我要定义的安全性
something explicitly and what happens is
明确地发生了什么，发生了什么
when you do that you you only change
当你这样做的时候，你只会改变
that part of you to configuration so if
您要配置的那部分，如果
i do something very simple of course you
我当然很简单
can do more stuff more complicated part
可以做更多更复杂的事情
there is in memory there is also gtv co
内存中还有gtv co
tification here so basically the simple
在这里设防基本上很简单
fact of defining that class will spring
定义该类的事实将产生
boot will detect it and will back off
开机将检测到它并退出
the auto configuration part that's
自动配置部分是
dealing with this because you define
处理这个，因为您定义
something yourself so we can we can
自己做些什么，以便我们可以
actually try while you're searching for
在尝试搜索时实际尝试
a different questions so let's say user
一个不同的问题，所以假设用户
total two goals you oh sorry user onion
一共两个目标，对不起，用户洋葱
okay let's try that so if I'm starting
好吧，让我们尝试一下，如果我开始
this up because the dead one is the
之所以这样，是因为死者是
authentication give 0 completely so I
身份验证完全给出0，所以我
should have user to tattoo somehow and
应该让用户以某种方式纹身和
you go so it does not flee answer the
你走了，所以它不会逃避回答
question because it's in memory but you
问题，因为它在内存中，但是您
basically get the full power of spring
基本上获得了弹簧的全部力量
security so you can if you want a
安全性，因此您可以根据需要
database backed authentication you can
数据库支持的身份验证可以
do so through the same mechanism okay
通过相同的机制这样做
here's another question we can can can
这是我们可以解决的另一个问题
we can figure the web server bundled
我们可以计算出捆绑的Web服务器
with spring boot with custom
定制弹簧靴
configuration I didn't get that let's
配置我没有得到，让我们
see here maybe I read it Rhonda it says
看到这里，也许我读了Rhonda，它说
uh yeah we can configure the web server
嗯，我们可以配置Web服务器
bundled with spring boot with custom
捆绑有定制的弹簧靴
configuration oh okay that one ok so
配置哦，好吧，一个就这样
there's basically two things you can do
您基本上可以做两件事
when you add the web starter so though
当您添加网络启动器时
the web technology in the withered you
网络技术使您枯萎
get tomcat by default so you can you can
默认情况下获取tomcat，以便您可以
decide to switch to something completely
决定完全切换到某种东西
different so you can use jet li or you
不同，所以您可以使用李连杰
can use an to toe if you want it's just
可以只用脚趾
replacing dependencies and you can also
替换依赖项，您还可以
configure things so if you want to know
配置事物，以便如果您想知道
what you can do you just type server dot
您可以做什么，只需输入服务器点
and you get all the configure
然后你得到所有的配置
shin of the embedded container there is
嵌入式容器的胫骨有
some Tomcat specific settings that you
您一些特定于Tomcat的设置
will find under server the Tomcat and
将在服务器下找到Tomcat和
you can find I believe in the tool as
您会发现我相信该工具
some support to I don't sing GT has no
我不唱歌的一些支持没有
it doesn't so here are all the key that
并非如此，这就是所有关键
you can define that will slightly change
您可以定义它会稍微改变
the way the Tomcat or the embedded
Tomcat或嵌入式的方式
container are installed you can also
容器已安装，您也可以
deploy deploy a spring boot up as a
部署将spring boot部署为
regular war file so if i go back to this
常规的战争档案，所以如果我回到这个
style springer dial quickly it's the
样式的弹力拨盘很快
same thing with IntelliJ IDEA by the way
顺便说一句，IntelliJ IDEA也是如此
you can decide to build a war file
你可以决定建立一个战争文件
instead of a jar file and that way to
而不是jar文件，这样
just build a regular war file that you
只需建立一个常规的战争文件，
can deploy in a nice orbit 3 container
可以部署在一个不错的3号轨道容器中
could I use H to counsel with other
我可以用H跟其他人咨询吗
databases nope so the h2 console is is
数据库没有，所以H2控制台是
something very specific that h2 provides
h2提供的非常具体的信息
and it really dedicated to h2 I don't
它真的致力于H2我不
think that you could use that with a
认为您可以将其与
different database although I might be
虽然我可能是不同的数据库
wrong but I would be surprised if that
错了，但是如果那会令我惊讶
was the case one might be a little bit
可能是一点点
of a longer answer but we've we've had
更长的答案，但我们已经
this question a couple times can you
这个问题好几次
tell us a bit about the spring boot and
告诉我们一些关于弹簧靴的信息，
spring road maps spring boot and what
春天的路线图春天的引导，什么
spring road maps oh sure so um
春天的路线图
springwood 1 the 2 dot 3 was released
springwood 1 2 dot 3已发布
today actually and we are currently
今天实际上，我们目前
working on the 1 2 3 release which will
在1 2 3版本上工作
be out around September this year so
今年九月左右出去
what we're going to do we have a set of
我们要做的是
themes that we want to to to implement
我们想要实现的主题
we want to implement caching
我们要实现缓存
auto-configuration so basically the
自动配置，所以基本上
ability to auto-detect a caching library
自动检测缓存库的能力
and provide the cache manager and cash
并提供缓存管理器和现金
statistics exposed cash statistics india
统计数据暴露现金统计印度
traitor we want to also improve the
叛徒我们还想改善
build tools that you use with a boot
构建用于引导的工具
mainly graydon has been improved with
主要是格雷登已经改善了
the used of the dependency plugin
依赖插件的使用
which allows you to use a million bum
允许您使用一百万烧
the same way maven so basically
同样地，行家也是如此
providing a reference to a bum and have
提供一个烧伤的参考，并有
the dependency management being applied
正在应用依赖项管理
to to your project we won also to update
到您的项目，我们也将更新
a plug-in so that it's easier for you to
一个插件，以便您更轻松地进行操作
run integration tests so basically does
基本上运行集成测试
a similar feature to cargo where you can
与货物类似的功能
start a spring good app run the
启动一个春季良好的应用程序运行
integration tests and then stop the
集成测试，然后停止
application regardless of the fact that
申请，无论事实
the desktop succeed or not and there is
桌面成功与否，还有
also plenty of other areas where we want
还有很多我们想要的其他领域
to improve the Giotto configuration
改善乔托配置
provide more options so that's what we
提供更多选择，这就是我们
busy doing at this point ok excellent so
在这一点上忙做还可以，所以
maybe maybe this is a 1 or less ones
也许这是1个或更少
here so why don't why don't you use
在这里，为什么不为什么不使用
Gradle is there some prattling grable
摇篮有一些碎裂的碎石
support and idea or maybe Gradle has
支持和想法，也许Gradle有
some disadvantages compared to maven um
与Maven um相比的一些缺点
no I I just use maven phone because I'm
没有II只是使用Maven手机，因为我
quite used to it i'm actually in the pmc
我已经习惯了pmc
so nathan is like some singer i've been
所以内森就像我去过的某个歌手
using for over 10 years great that is
使用了10多年了
just fine so you can see you can use
很好，所以您可以看到可以使用
that in the resort and you'll get the
在度假村，你会得到
same experience can do that actually
相同的经验可以做到这一点
right away so you can do create a new
马上就可以创建一个新的
project spiritual Iser you can say i
项目精神伊塞尔，你可以说我
want a credit project instead can use
想要一个信贷项目，而是可以使用
all the same options have any web
所有相同的选项都有网络
security West whatever GPA actuator h 2
安全西部无论GPA执行器h 2
demo gradient and create that as a new
演示渐变并将其创建为新的
window so you get the same user
窗口，以便您获得相同的用户
experience IntelliJ IDEA detecting that
体验IntelliJ IDEA检测到的
a greater project needs to be considered
需要考虑更大的项目
for you and then it will do the well you
为你，然后它会做得很好
will get the usual greater support
将获得通常的更大支持
within intellij idea
intellij的想法
as far as food is concerned we have
就食物而言
built begins for both so we have a
两者都开始建造，所以我们有一个
built-in for maven and a plug-in for
内置的Maven和一个插件
later and we try as much as we can to
稍后，我们将尽力而为
have the same features between the two I
我两个之间有相同的特征
was mentioning the dependency a plug-in
提到依赖性插件
in greater which allows you to use an
在更大的程度上，您可以使用
event pom right from your Gradle script
直接从Gradle脚本中获取事件pom
this is something that that's not
这不是什么
supported out of the box that greater
开箱即用的支持更大
does not support and with we felt that
不支持，我们感到
it was really annoying as then you have
真的很烦人
to define versions whereas you could
定义版本，而你可以
simply use a proper dependency
只需使用适当的依赖项
management so we actually build a
管理，所以我们实际上建立了一个
plug-in ourselves and that's what we use
自己插入，这就是我们使用的
now as from spring 203 so you can see
现在是从203年春季开始，所以您可以看到
that as you can guess I'm not using
如您所料，我没有使用
ridden much so it's not moving a few a
骑了很多，所以它不动了一些
few things here but it's a perfectly
这里的东西很少，但这是完美的
valid project thank you Stefan a couple
有效的项目，谢谢斯特凡夫妇
links here well we wrap up again Stefan
链接在这里很好，我们再次总结斯特凡
thank you so much for your time and
非常感谢您的宝贵时间，
thank you everybody for joining us and
谢谢大家加入我们
it was a pleasure having you we look
很高兴看到你
forward to having you visit us again
期待您再次访问我们